<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[OC Lore Project]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>OC Lore Project</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 15:58:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 15:58:37 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[AMF]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Home Directory" data-href="Home Directory" href="poly-lore-project\home-directory.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">&lt;- Home</a><br><br><br><br>Founded shortly after the implosion of the soviet union by soviet oligarchs, AMF quickly rose to dominate the Eastern European underground arms trade due to the surplus of weaponry now left idle in the many remote military stations from St Petersburg to Yakutsk. During the first decade of the company's operations contracts and dealings were relatively mundane, with the majority of operations being that of private security, training and advisory for less experienced European countries (specifically the Baltic states) and asset protection. <br>However, as the company began to expand, and as technology as it pertains to warfare began to evolve in the early years of the new millennium, AMF began its operations across the Atlantic. With the presence of a Russian founded mercenary group operating on American soil being almost impossible, obfuscation and regulatory loopholes were required to continue this operation. <br><br>In October of 2003, a separate company was founded primarily based in research, and not on overt militaristic activity. Despite the change in stated operation, AMF still actively hired and was allowed to operate (with extreme regulation) on American soil as private security for those that could afford it. This included the acquisition of licences to operate military grade firearms and equipment.<br>
Although deniable as of the present day, it is speculated that since as early as the mid 2000s, AMF has received funding through indirect means through both CCP and Russian channels.<br>
AMF as a company has been incredibly successful in their research endeavours, filing multiple lucrative patents throughout the late 2000s ranging from advanced radar tech, anti-air munitions specifically designed to counter the growing use of drones in aerial warfare.<br><br>In November 2015, AMF operated satellites over central Europe detected an object entering the atmosphere at Mach 8.7, quickly altering its trajectory in a way unlike any before it. Upon noticing that this object was not decreasing in mass upon entry into the atmosphere, a team of personnel was sent to the projected landing site at [REDACTED] northeast of the town of [REDACTED]. When asked for public comment, AMF Spokesmen in conjunction with the government of [REDACTED] stated that the object was a regular small meteorite with nothing out of the ordinary.<br>
What was recovered is unknown, however in the years that followed, AMF's rollout of patents and technology collaborations would slow to a crawl.<br>
Details of this project are kept incredibly classified, with the board of shareholders only knowing it by name and it not existing on public record, and being assured that whatever losses the company may incur by having their top scientists working almost entirely on it was more than worth it.<br>
Whatever was shown behind closed doors was enough to keep the stock price afloat. <br><img alt="archangel.png" src="lib\media\archangel.png" style="width: 450px; max-width: 100%;"><br><br>
<br>Project Archangel is the reverse engineering of an entity discovered at the 2015 crash site.
<br>The Entity is to be contained in a locked cell 150m underground within the [REDACTED] facility under 24 hour surveillance. 
<br>The Entity can communicate in a way understandable to humans, and has agreed to cooperate in the development of reverse engineering its technology with the agreement that it is used for a noble cause. 
<br>The primary effect being replicated is the alteration of the state of an entity's physical scale. The entity possesses the ability to grow and shrink its self and others at will. This effect does not extend to inanimate objects, excluding any matter in direct contact with the organic matter of the subject effected.
<br>The effect is not chemical, thermal or radiation based, but appears to effect the electromagnetic effect of the subject during the process.

<br>Shrinking organic matter can be done with a magnetic pulse not too dissimilar to an EMP.


<br>The effect has been duplicated independent of the entity as of 2021, but with major drawbacks that only make it suitable for limited operations as an offensive weapon.

<br>Subjects can be shrunk to 1/175th scale, but the effect only lasts for as long as 26hrs, with the effect lasting on average about 23 hours.

<br>This is currently used for covert espionage operations.


<br>Subjects can be grown to 15x their original scale, however the effect only lasts on average 15m. However this has shown to vary wildly depending on an individuals tolerance (what determines this tolerance is currently unknown).
<br>Subjects do not maintain durability at smaller sizes, and shows the same effects on the human sensory system as <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Equinox > Project Asthenis" data-href="Equinox#Project Asthenis" href="poly-lore-project\equinox.html#Project_Asthenis" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Equinox's Asthenis Project</a>.


<br><br>
<br>As of January 9th, 2023, AMF has lost control of the entity, its whereabouts unknown. This is a direct result of a leak caused by a former employee that informed the entity of the purpose of the research and the corporation's intent to use it as a weapon. 
<br>Said employee cannot be killed at this time, as a dead mans switch is in place that if triggered, is speculated to leak the details of Project Archangel to the press.
<br>As of today, AMF has two primary objectives.<br>
<br>AMF are currently looking for a way to make the scale altering aspect of the technology cheaper as right now it is unsustainably expensive to maintain.
<br>AMF are searching to either recapture the entity, or find a suitable replacement.
]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\amf.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/AMF.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:37:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\archangel.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\archangel.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Artwork + Story Gallery]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Home Directory" data-href="Home Directory" href="poly-lore-project\home-directory.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">&lt;- Home</a><br>]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\artwork-+-story-gallery.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/Artwork + Story Gallery.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:02:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CGL]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>CGL is the acronym given to a university thesis by a single researcher out of NY. Not much is known about the paper other than it's abstract, however it is known that Dr. Amy Kobayashi is credited on the abstract for the paper as a contributor. The original paper has been scrubbed from the internet as well as the researcher's location at this time. <br>Paper Abstract: (Taken from Wayback Machine)<br>
Investigating the use of concentrated, refracted gamma radiation on the molecular structure of organic material, as well as the use of this procedure as a way to create memetic captures of a the human consciousness. It is theorized that the "miniaturization" of organic matter allowed by this procedure will make the ability to create rewritable "snapshots" of the human memory possible through rapid...
<br>Webpage unarchived beyond this point, the rest of the abstract is obscured by a "read more" JavaScript button which dynamically loaded content, making its archival impossible at the time of capture.<br><br>
<br>The paper outlines a procedure that creates an identical clone of a subject using radioactive "photogrammetry" to create a snapshot of what equates to a human soul. This data can then be rasterized and copied into a vessel of choice.
<br>The consciousness data exists in two states:

<br>As a radioactive signature created by the [REDACTED] process. Referred to as Copy A-1.
<br>As a Digital state copied from A-1, this is static and unchanging, known as A-2.


<br>State A-1 dynamically changes, whether this be through quantum entanglement or some other mechanism is unknown.
<br>Before a subject is cloned, a digital (A-2) copy of the consciousness is created which appears to contain all of the memories of that "soul" at the time of the digital copy's creation. 
<br>An unfortunate side effect of this process is upon creation of A-1, the dynamic copy, the original host dies.
<br>It is speculated that the ability to transfer a mock consciousness was tested before the researcher conducted the procedure on themselves.
<br>At this time, the researcher exists in a state of perpetual death, copy and transfer. The motives for this are unknown, but is speculated to be some kind of accelerated natural selection/evolution process.
<br>As of this time, CGL is on the radar of both <a data-href="AMF" href="poly-lore-project\amf.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">AMF</a> and <a data-href="Equinox" href="poly-lore-project\equinox.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Equinox</a> however AMF appear to be delving deeper into the matter, sending multiple archival retrieval requests to the university for the original paper.<br>Meta Note
CGL is mostly peripheral to the main plot, and exists mainly in self contained scenarios.
]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\cgl.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/CGL.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 10:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Character Types and Guidelines]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Home Directory" data-href="Home Directory" href="poly-lore-project\home-directory.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">&lt;- Home</a><br><br><br>Characters within this universe exist in two distinct categories, designed to allow for easy collaboration with other artists and or friends that wish to collaborate in any way. This universe is meant to house primarily OCs that belong to specific people, not established characters from existing media.<br><br>
<br>Characters that I have made and/or have ownership of, these characters have this universe as their "base" reality, with events that take place within it affecting their canon.
<br>Characters that were not made by me, but were made specifically for this universe. Although the main universe of this character is this one, if the creator of said character wishes to have them exist outside of it in other pieces or stories then I have no objections or retain any of the rights to said character.
<br><br>
<br>Characters that I do not own or have the rights to, unless stated otherwise by the respective owner this universe has no affect on the canon behaviour of said character. These characters can be retconned at any time but as a request please don't have them have too much impact on the storyline if you see this being a possibility down the line.
<br>These characters can act in any way that their owners wish so long as they adhere to the lore of this storyline.
<br>The best way to think of these characters are almost "cameos" that could either be one offs, or have a significant impact on the trajectory of the storyline.
<br>By default, characters exist as "alternate universe" instances of themselves, however if you wish for characters to be "teleported" or be transported to this universe in some kind of supernatural event that's also fine. Or if you're not too fussed at all and just want these characters to exist as their normal selves that's cool too.
<br><br>
<br>The rules of this setting are pretty relaxed, supernatural powers, events and "magic" of sorts can exist, just as long as these don't cause world altering events or destruction anything goes.
<br>As for size, characters are allowed to magically grow/shrink at will if that character possesses that ability, however if they are relatively normal then they must follow the in universe <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Size Tech" data-href="Size Tech" href="poly-lore-project\size-tech.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">size tech</a>.
]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\character-types-and-guidelines.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/Character Types and Guidelines.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 11:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Equinox]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Home Directory" data-href="Home Directory" href="poly-lore-project\home-directory.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">&lt;- Home</a><br><br><br>Founded in 2006, equinox is an American owned and operated private military company with a research division that hires an incredibly large amount of former government employees. It has long been speculated that Equinox has deep ties to the US government, with many top executives being former members of the intelligence community.<br>
Equinox was formed as a direct response to <a data-href="AMF" href="poly-lore-project\amf.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">AMF</a>, another company operating on US soil with similar goals, output, and an equally as impressive history of impressive patents Equinox has close ties to the US, even being involved with the DARPA HTV-2 Project in 2011 (although uncredited).<br>Despite Equinox being primarily known within the scientific community for their patents, the majority of its revenue comes from private military contract work, with Equinox having the majority of the PMC market share in most of the South American continent, Canada, and parts of the far east. Equinox is the only private military company for example to have presence in the first island chain to the east of China. Domestic PMCs in these countries exist of course, but take primarily "low" status jobs from crime lords and corrupt local politicians. Almost all high end contracts are handled by Equinox employed mercenaries.<br>
This insanely lucrative income stream and dominance of the Asian and South American PMC contract market share, coupled with suspected backing by the intelligence community has positioned Equinox to almost be an almost unofficial branch of the US military. Their only rival being that of AMF, which dominates the European market share.<br><br>In November 2015, researchers at an Equinox Research lab in Arizona discovered that by distilling and boiling in a very specific vacuum 6 different chemical compounds (3 of which are patented by Equinox themselves) in a process not too dissimilar to the manufacturing of Aerogel that a substance could be made that rapidly collapsed the distance between molecules it interacted with. The compound was named "Sarvus" or "SVS-8" internally, and was researched in the coming years as a side project with it originally intended to be used to transport cargo much more efficiently.<br>However, by the end of 2020, Project Sarvus, under the guidance of Dr. Amy Kobayashi had reached a stage where a version of the compound could be synthesized that when administered orally, or as a gas with a similar consistency and colour to chlorine gas, could render organic matter from 1:8th to 1:250th in scale depending on the concentration of the substance.<br><br>
<br>Upon ingestion of the compound (SVS-8) the subject rapidly shrinks in scale, along with any and all belongings in contact with the subject.

<br>It is for this reason that tests are conducted with an aerosol, rather than ingested orally.


<br>Subjects are observed to remain fully conscious throughout the process, only reporting mild nausea after the compound has fully taken effect. However it is unclear if this nausea is as a result of the procedure, or is simply motion sickness as a result of the drastic perspective difference that occurs at such scales.
<br>The effect can be reversed with an anti-compound of sorts, without this, the scale of the subject remains constant and permanent.
<br>Subjects can only be shrunk, not grown.
<br>It is confirmed that <a data-href="AMF" href="poly-lore-project\amf.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">AMF</a> knows of the project, and have sent mercenaries to attempt to sabotage the research unsuccessfully on one occasion.
<br>Beyond a certain concentration, this effect stops, 1:250th being the upper limit. It is speculated that this is because the body can no longer effectively absorb the compounds particulates at this scale.
<br>Subjects DO NOT maintain durability at smaller scales, early tests involved the injury of numerous participants during initial trials.
<br>Subjects report an increased sense of smell and taste, with the smaller the scale, the more intense these sensations.
]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\equinox.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/Equinox.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 12:43:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Information]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br>
<br>A while ago I thought it would be a neat idea to connect renders that I've made with my own characters in a shared storyline. Why? Because creative writing is a fun part of this hobby and it's a neat extra layer of detail for those that pay attention. This collection of pages is intended to serve as a hub mainly for myself to ensure that there's some degree of coherence and consistency across renders that take place within this "universe".
<br>As I shared proof of concepts, some people expressed an interest in having their characters interact with this universe. Others I reached out to with an interest in including their characters as one offs or cameos. If you want to know how external OCs exist within this setting, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Character Types and Guidelines" data-href="Character Types and Guidelines" href="poly-lore-project\character-types-and-guidelines.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">read this</a>.
<br><br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Summary" data-href="Summary" href="poly-lore-project\summary.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Summary (Start Here)</a><br><br>
<br><a data-href="Character Types and Guidelines" href="poly-lore-project\character-types-and-guidelines.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Character Types and Guidelines</a>
<br><a data-href="Size Tech" href="poly-lore-project\size-tech.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Size Tech</a>
<br><br><br><br>
<br><a data-href="Female" href="Female" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Female</a>
<br><a data-href="Male" href="Male" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Male</a>
<br><br>
<br><a data-href="Equinox" href="poly-lore-project\equinox.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Equinox</a>
<br><a data-href="AMF" href="poly-lore-project\amf.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">AMF</a>
<br><a data-href="US Government" href="poly-lore-project\us-government.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">US Government</a>
<br><a data-href="CGL" href="poly-lore-project\cgl.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">CGL</a>
<br><br>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Kill Counts (Female).canvas" data-href="Kill Counts (Female).canvas" href="poly-lore-project\kill-counts\kill-counts-(female).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kill Counts (Female)</a>
<br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Kill Counts (Male).canvas" data-href="Kill Counts (Male).canvas" href="poly-lore-project\kill-counts\kill-counts-(male).html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Kill Counts (Male)</a>
]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\home-directory.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/Home Directory.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 15:58:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Size Tech]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Home Directory" data-href="Home Directory" href="poly-lore-project\home-directory.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">&lt;- Home</a><br><br><br>
<br>Faster Activating (almost instant), not chemical based, wears off in about a day for shrink, in a couple hours for growth.
<br>Relies on an otherworldly entity for further development. 
<br>Process is incredibly energy intensive, and currently extremely expensive.
<br>Entity responsible for it's creation no longer under AMF control.
<br>Development has plateaued at a point where there are these drawbacks, all efforts now focused on making it cheaper.
<br>Subjects are extremely delicate when small, but extremely strong when large.
<br>Effect can be used offensively in the form of electromagnetic pulses, however this requires specialized equipment that needs to be mounted to a vehicle to be portable at all.
<br><br>
<br>Acts over about 30s.
<br>Still rather expensive, but chemical based so can be manufactured.
<br>Subjects are still extremely delicate when small.
<br>Effect does not wear off unless an anti-compound is administered.
<br>Subjects can shrink smaller than Project Archangel, with the limit being 1/250 rather than 1/175.
<br>Effect can be used offensively in the form of gas grenades or poison.
<br><br>
<br>Radiation Based, Cheap
<br>Irreversible.
<br>Results in a loss of original body, an ability to clone a vessel is needed for it to be effective.
<br>Memories are transferred between "lives" via a quantum entanglement like phenomena altering the original capture as the current clone creates new memories.
]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\size-tech.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/Size Tech.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 13:01:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Plot Premise]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Home Directory" data-href="Home Directory" href="poly-lore-project\home-directory.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">&lt;- Home</a><br><br><br>The setting is a modern day conspiracy thriller that follows a corporate cold war between two rival corporations that have both cracked size altering tech at around the same time. Both of these corporations currently operate within the United States.<br>
<a data-href="AMF" href="poly-lore-project\amf.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">AMF</a> is the first of these corporations, founded soon after the collapse of the USSR they came to dominate the European PMC market by the turn of the millennium. Eventually expanding to operate on US soil in the early 2000s by the time the story takes place, they have an incredible history of weapons and tech patents. The group has suspected ties to both the Russian Government and the CCP although these ties are unconfirmed.<br>
This group cracked size tech through reverse engineering an entity of unknown origin, the project was named <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="AMF > Project Archangel" data-href="AMF#Project Archangel" href="poly-lore-project\amf.html#Project_Archangel" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Project Archangel</a> and has reached a stage where an inferior version of the entity's abilities can be replicated independent of it.<br>
The second of these organizations is <a data-href="Equinox" href="poly-lore-project\equinox.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Equinox</a>, an American owned and operated PMC founded in 2006 as a direct response to <a data-href="AMF" href="poly-lore-project\amf.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">AMF</a>'s growing market share. They have a similarly impressive history of patents and research and cracked size tech through <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Equinox > Project Sarvus" data-href="Equinox#Project Sarvus" href="poly-lore-project\equinox.html#Project_Sarvus" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Project Sarvus</a>. Much like their competitor's equivalent, it too comes with extensive drawbacks.<br>
The story follows as a main plot both corporations' attempts to sabotage the other through espionage and other shady methods.<br>
Although this is the primary plot, the setting allows for numerous tangential subplots that have little or no relation at all to the main storyline.]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\summary.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/Summary.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 13:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US Government]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Home Directory" data-href="Home Directory" href="poly-lore-project\home-directory.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">&lt;- Home</a><br><br><br>Within the context of the setting, the US government has close ties to <a data-href="Equinox" href="poly-lore-project\equinox.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Equinox</a>, with a large number of executives within the company being former Intelligence committee. Although directly funding Equinox through research grants and corporate donations, the US's interest in the company lies primarily with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Equinox > Project Sarvus" data-href="Equinox#Project Sarvus" href="poly-lore-project\equinox.html#Project_Sarvus" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Project Sarvus</a>. The US Government has access to the technology in house, and uses it primarily for surveillance of persons of interest.<br>
As for public record the US Government denies any involvement with Equinox to a level beyond that of any other private company.]]></description><link>poly-lore-project\us-government.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Poly Lore Project/US Government.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 13:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>